Anything can happen when you're in ... Virgin Territory
Virgin Territory is a adventure, action, comedy film directed by David Leland.
In Black Death era Tuscany, as in the Decameron, ten young
Florentines take refuge from the plague.
But instead of telling stories, they have lusty adventures, bawdy exchanges,
romance, swordplay, randy nuns, Saracen pirates, and a sexy cow.
Lorenzo, played by Hayden Christensen.
Pampinea, played by Mischa Barton.
Elissa, played by Kate Groombridge.
Filomena, played by Rosalind Halstead.
Gerbino, played by Tim Roth.
Count Dzerzhinsky, played by Matthew Rhys.
Virgin Territory is a 2007 romantic comedy film directed by David Leland.
It was the last film produced by Dino De Laurentiis.
The film stars Hayden Christensen, Mischa Barton, Tim
Roth, Rosalind Halstead and
Kate Groombridge.
It is based upon Giovanni Boccaccio's 14th-century tale The Decameron.
The film was released in France on December 12, 2007.
The film explores themes of tuscany, italy, sex
comedy, black death, plague, 14th century.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.